hahaha.com 2012-10-31

# Privacy Policy | Just For Laughs

###  HAHAHA.COM Privacy Policy and protection of personal information

This Privacy Policy and protection of personal information (hereinafter: « **Privacy Policy** ») sets out Just for laughs. (hereinafter: « **the Company** ») practices for the collection, use or disclosure of personal information through the use of the online services available on its websiteHAHAHA.COM. **The website HAHAHA.COM is operated and hosted in Montreal, province of Quebec, Canada. If you are a visitor from abroad and that you provide personal information, you agree that your personal information be transferred and hosted in the province of Quebec and protected by the applicable laws in this province.**

  **A-Personal information**  
The Company only collects personal information from a user of the online servicesof the website HAHAHA.COM,on a voluntary basis. Personal information may include: your name, date of birth, mail address, phone number, e-mail, sms, credit card number, etc. Such information which identifies you personally is collected only when voluntarily submitted by a user in one of our online information registration forms or within e-mail correspondence.  
For example, to have access to the services of the website HAHAHA.COM, user must complete a user profile to become a Member of the website where certain information is collected such as name, age, email address of the user and other information. Once this profile completed, the Company may ask you other information related to the services provided. Thus, if you buy products on the online store of the website HAHAHA.COM, we will ask you information about your credit card, home address and other information allowing us to transfer you the ownership of the products purchased on the online store of the website HAHAHA.COM and to comply with the laws and regulations governing the sale of products over the Internet.

  **B- The purpose of the collection**  
The purpose of the personal information we collect is to identify you when you navigate on the website HAHAHA.COM, to satisfy your request of services and to provide you with certain services or advertisements offers that meet your personal needs.

    **C-Disclosure to Third Parties**  
It is the Company's policy not to disclose any personal information about users of the websiteHAHAHA.COMto third parties, theinformation transmitted being only available to the Company or its affiliates companies, as the case may be.  
Also the Company will not disclose, sell or rent to any third party or organization, for marketing purposes, any personal information you provide on this website without your prior permission.  
It is possible that the Company may make available personal information of its Members to well-known companies or connected with the artists appearing on the website HAHAHA.COM whose products and services may interest you. You can indicate your acceptance or rejection of such a communication when you receive notice of a communication to a particular third party. If you refuse, you will not receive and enjoy the offerings of the third party.  
However, the Company reserves its right to disclose personal information about you if required by law or if court orders are issued, including receipt of a subpoena or a search warrant. The Company reserves its right to disclose any information it deems necessary in good faith i) to comply with any requirement of law or legal process, ii) enforce HAHAHA.COMUser Agreement, or iii) to protect the rights of its other Members.  
The Company also limits the access to your personal information only to employees of certain departments (ex. delivery, finance) who need to know to facilitate your transactionsor respond to the correspondence you may send us in the course of your usage of the website HAHAHA.COM.

  **D-Use of cookies**  
THE COMPANY uses cookie technology (cookies) to help Members navigate faster on the websiteHAHAHA.COM. When you register on our website, we download a cookie on your computer. A cookie is a string of information that is sent by a website and stored on the hard drive or temporarily in the memory of your computer. This technology allows faster navigation and a generally more positive experience when searching the information you want. **You can disable cookies by disabling this feature in your browser**.

  **E-Information collected**  
Our web servers collect monitoring and general information from your visit on our website.We collect such statistics data to determine anonymous patterns of browsing,the number of daily visitors to our website, the daily requests for a particular file, the types of browsers used by users, the users' domain names and countries of origin. This data helps us to personalize our website to better meet your online needs.

  **F-Storage & Security**  
All personal information you provide to the Company are stored on our secure servers with restricted access. In deciding to voluntarily provide us your personal information, you agree to the transfer and storage of your personal data on our servers located in Montreal, Province of Quebec, Canada.  
The Company takes reasonable technical means to ensure a safe environment and protect user data.  
however, given the public nature of the internet network, user acknowledges and agrees that the security of communications through the internet cannot be guaranteed. therefore, the company cannot guarantee nor shall bear any liability for any breach of confidentiality, hacking, viruses, loss or alteration of information transmitted or hosted on the company’s systems.

  **G- User’s Responsibilities**  
If you associate your name with your access code, people to whom you have revealed your name will identify you and your activities on our website. The company is not responsible for any loss or damage sustained by user, resulting from disclosure, intentional or not, of its access codeor for personal information revealed by the user.  
You agree to use your user’s information only to obtain online services offered on the website HAHAHA.COM (ex. use of the blog room provided on the website, transactions related to the onlinestore, etc.).  
You are not authorized to add other users on your account.  
You cannot use the communication tools provided by the Company to transmit spam or any other content that violates the User Agreement of the website HAHAHA.COM.  
You are not authorized to disclose your password to anyone which must remain confidential. If you decide to share it with others, you will be responsible for any action taken under your account.  
If you believe that your password has been compromised in any manner whatsoever, you must notify the Company immediately and change your password.  
You agree to keep updated your personal information if it changes or is no longer relevant.  
At all times, user remains fully responsible for any loss or damages caused to the company or a third party resulting from any activity generated under its access code or its user’s account even in case of loss of confidentiality or illegal use.

    **H-Storage**  
At your request or upon termination of your subscription, we will close your account and delete your personal information.  
Despite the closure of your account, we reserve the right to keep, for an indefinite period of time within the time limits specified in the applicable Quebec laws, some personal information to be in compliance with the law, prevent fraud, collect fees owed, resolve a claim or some other related problems, cooperate in an investigation, enforce the User Agreement and any other act permitted by law.  
At the end of this period, the data files will be destroyed or deleted from the Company’s system, with the exception of anonymous statistical data that the Company may retain, at its discretion, as long as sought.  
Particularly, the Company will retain for a period of six (6) months from the date of receipt of a notice of claimed infringementsent by the holder of copyright, a recordallowing the identity of the person to whom the electronic location belongs to be determined and if the claimant commences proceedings relating to the claimed infringement and so notifies the Company before the end of those six months, for one (1) year from the date of receipt of a notice of the claimed infringement.

**I-Additional Information**  
You can view, edit and modify most of your personal information online by connecting to our website: [www.hahaha.com](http://www.hahaha.com/ "www.hahaha.com")  
For any questions, comments or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy, you may do so by contacting us by email or mail to:

General Email: [info@hahaha.com](mailto:info@hahaha.com)

Mailing Address:  
Just For Laughs  
2101 St. Laurent Blvd.  
Montreal, Quebec H2X 2T5

Phone Number: (514) 845-3440 ext. 2420

**J-References by hyperlinks**  
The navigation on the website HAHAHA.COM offers links to other websites. However, we are not responsible for the content or practices employed by the organizations sponsoring these other websites. The company is not responsible for the practices, acts or policies of such third parties with respect to the protection of your personal information.We recommend that you carefully read the statement on the protection of personal information found on these websites in order to determine in an informed manner to what extent you want or not to use these websites regarding their privacy practice.

**K- Modification**  
The Company reserves its right to modify this Privacy Policy at its discretion.However, any change to this statement will be made in accordance with the laws applicable in the province of Quebec for the protection of personal information.  
The Company will make available on the website HAHAHA.COM, any amendments to this Privacy Policy at least thirty (30) days before the date of entry into force.  
The Company will also notify the Member by email at least thirty (30) days before the entry into force of an amendment to this Use Agreement. The notice sent by the Company will reflect the new provision or amendment to a provision, as well as its earlier version and date of entry into force. The notice given will reflect the Member's right to terminate the contract without cost, penalty or termination fee, by sending e-mail written notice to the Company within thirty (30) days from the date of force of the amendment if the amendment results in the increase in the obligation of the Member or the reduction of the obligation of the Company.  
In the event that user would not accept the changes or would be dissatisfied with any decision or policy adopted by the Company in operating the services, your only recourse is to terminate the HAHAHA.COM User agreement by giving a written notice to the Company by email and stop using the services of the site,without any liability of the Company towards you or any third party, resulting from your termination of the services of the website HAHAHA.COM.  
This Privacy Policy is subject to all the terms and conditions for the use of the website provided in the online document entitled: HAHAHA.COM ONLINE USER AGREEMENT.
